I am just trying to move on with my life.
我只是努力振作起来继续生活
Are you having an affair with my husband?
你是不是和我丈夫有一腿?
Suspicion ended in tragedy.
(猜疑的结果是悲剧)
I'm here to see Rex Van De Kamp. Apparently, he had a heart attack.
嗯, 不好意思, 我来探望Rex Van De Kamp 他好像是心脏病发作了
Trust...
(信任...)
It kills me that I'm putting you through this.
让你受这种苦, 我心里真是难过
was put on trial.
(经受严峻的考验)
Bring me the passport, and Mr. Solis can visit his mother.
把护照交给我, Solis先生就能去 探望他母亲了
And ex-husband
(前夫)
She is out there throwing herself at Mike Delfino
她在那儿向Mike Delfino投怀送抱
And everyone
(每一个人)
Wow, your own personal nanny? Smell you.
喔, 你的家庭保姆? 不错啊
was getting in over their heads.
(忙于他们自己的事情)
Edie Britt could never understand why she didn't have any female friends.
(Edie Britt永远都不会明白为什么 她一个女性朋友都没有)
Of course, she always tried to tell people she didn't need any,
(当然, 她一直试图告诉人们她一个 也不需要)
but the truth was
(但事实上)
it bothered Edie that other women didn't seem to like her.
(其它女人都不喜欢她让Edie觉得很困扰)
Even after moving to Wisteria Lane...
(甚至在搬到Wisteria Lane之后...)
oh, and be careful. There are breakables in there.
哦, 当心点, 里面是易碎品
Edie couldn't understand why her neighbors kept their distance.
(Edie不明白为什么她的邻居们 始终和她保持距离)
And then she met Martha Huber.
(后来她遇到了Martha Huber)
Hola.
你好
Within five minutes, Mrs. Huber managed to disparage what Edie was wearing.
(在五分钟之内Huber夫人就成功地 贬低了Edie的穿着)
No
不行
In fact, whenever they got together, Mrs. Huber insulted her.
(事实上, 只要她们在一起, Huber夫人就侮辱她)
She made fun of everything from Edie's makeup...
(她取笑Edie的一切, 从化妆...)
to her taste in men.
(到对男人的品味)
Yes, Martha Huber could be cruel, offensive, and downright mean,
(是的, Martha Huber可说是残忍的, 无礼的 彻头彻尾吝啬的)
but Edie didn't care, because she was the first real friend Edie Britt had ever had.
(但Edie并不介意, 因为她是Edie Britt 第一个真正的朋友)
But now Martha Huber was missing. She had vanished without a trace,
(但现在Martha Huber失踪了, 消失得不留痕迹)
and Edie was not embarrassed to admit she needed her back.
(Edie可以毫不尴尬地承认, 她需要她回来)
Edie?
Yes.
是的
I'm Felicia Tilman,
我是Felicia Tilman
Martha's sister.
Martha的妹妹
Really?
真的?
What's wrong?
有什么不对吗?
Oh, nothing's wrong. It's just that Martha always said how alike you two were.
哦, 没什么. 只是Martha一直说 你们两个很相像
I just don't seethe family resemblance.
我只是没看到家族的相似性
It's there. It just takes a while to become apparent.
那的确有. 只是需要一点时间去发现
Do you have the key to her house?
你有她房子的钥匙吗?
I do. After the police kicked the door in, they put on this temporary lock.
我有. 在警察破门而入之后 他们装了这个临时的锁
Oh, and by the way, the neighbors are coming over at noon.
哦, 对了, 邻居们会在中午过来
We're going to organize and hand out flyers.
我们将组织起来发送传单
the key?
钥匙?
Oh, right.
哦, 对了
You know, I can only imagine how worried you must be.
我知道你现在非常的担心
I'm not worried, Edie.
我不担心, Edie
Martha and I have a very intense bond. We were connected at the most primal level,
Martha和我有紧密的联系. 我们在最根本的层面上相互连接
and a few days ago, I felt this sensation in my soul.
几天前, 我感应到了一些东西
That's when it first dawned on me that something had happened to my sister,
那时候我第一次觉察到我姐姐出事了
and then when she didn't arrive at my home as scheduled,
后来我姐姐没有按计划来我家
well, that's when I knew she was dead.
从那时起我知道她死了
Oh, honey, no. You mustn't think like that.
哦, 亲爱的, 不. 你不应该那样想
Martha's only missing.
Martha只是失踪了
No, Edie. She's dead.
不, Edie. 她死了
But she's my sister, and I'm going to find out exactly what happened to her.
不过他是我姐姐, 我会发现到底 她发生了什么事
Look, Felicia, it's natural to freak out when a loved one's missing.
我说, Felicia, 当一个你爱的人 失踪的时候行为失常是很自然的
Loved one?
我爱的人?
Oh. Edie, let me be clear about this
Edie, 我就明说了吧
-
I hated Martha.
我恨Martha
She was a wretched pig of a woman, and the day she died, this world became a better place.
她是一头肮脏的母猪, 她死的那天 世界会变得更美好
It was in that moment that Edie finally saw the family resemblance.
(就在那一刻Edie终于看到了家族的相似性)
Episode 11 : Move On
第十一集 : 继续前进
Mrs. Huber was missing.
(Huber夫人失踪了)
The words echoed down Wisteria Lane until every last resident was aware of her disappearance.
(这个消息回荡在Wisteria Lane直到 最后一个居民也知道了她失踪的事)
By noon, dozens of neighbors had gathered.
(中午的时候, 众多的邻居聚集在一起)
Some came to volunteer.
(有些人来做志愿者)
Some came in sympathy.
(有些人出于同情而来)
And some came to learn exactly what the police knew
(而有些人则是来了解警察到底知道什么)
and what they didn't.
(不知道什么)
So I'll need you to pass out flyers.
我要你们发放传单
Put them in the mall, the park, anywhere you think Mrs. Huber might have been seen.
把它们放在商场, 公园, 任何你觉得 Huber夫人可能被看到过的地方
We need to jump on this. Time is of the essence.
我们要动作快点, 时间宝贵
Edie, would you like to say something?
Edie, 你想说几句吗?
On behalf of Martha and her sister Felicia,
我代表Martha和她的sister Felicia
I'd like to thank you all for coming here today.
谢谢你们大家今天能够来到这里
You know, my last conversation with Martha was one of anger,
我和Martha的最后一次交谈充满怒气
and I'll never forgive myself for the things that I said.
我永远不能原谅我所说的事情
I lay awake at night thinking about it.
我晚上睡不着觉, 一直想着那个
I don't know how she did it, but Edie managed to make this all about her.
我不知道她怎么做的, 但Edie成功地 把这事变成了她的个人表演
She's a talented girl, our Edie.
我们的Edie, 她是个天才
Has anybody talked to Bree? How's Rex doing?
有谁和Bree说过话了吗? Rex怎么样了?
She's bringing him home from the hospital today.
她今天把他从医院接回家里
Boy, I don't know how he had a heart attack. He was so young.
我真不知道他怎么会有心脏病 他还那么年轻
Hey, how creepy is Mrs. Huber's sister?
嗨, Huber夫人的妹妹好古怪啊
I know.
我知道
The way she was talking about Mrs. Huber, it was like she was already dead.
她谈论Huber夫人的方式就好像她已经死了
You don't think she's...
难道你不觉得她...
oh, no. I'm sure she's fine. We're talking about Mrs. Huber.
哦, 不. 我敢肯定她没事 我们可是在说Huber夫人啊
She's like a roach.
她像蟑螂那样有生命力
I just wanted you to know that everyone on Wisteria Lane is praying for your sister's safe return.
我想让你知道Wisteria Lane的每个人 都在祈祷你的sister能够平安归来
Oh, I seriously doubt that.
哦, 我很怀疑
What do you mean, you're not taking care of him?
你说你不会照看他, 你是什么意思?
Dad's being released today. He's got to have a place to recuperate.
爸爸今天出院, 他应该有个地方休养
Well, then, he can go to a motel, because he is not allowed back in my house.
那么他可以去住旅馆 因为我不允许他回到我的家里
I thought you two were getting along. What happened?
我以为你们两个和好了. 发生了什么事?
T hat's...
那个...
between your father and me.
是我和你爸爸之间的事
You're so selfish.
你真自私
You know, I am so looking forward to the day that I get to put you in a nursing home.
我真是期待送你进疗养院的那一天啊
but my plan is to have an embolism and to die young.
但我的计划是得一次栓塞 在年轻的时候就死去
Yeah, well, we're all rooting for you, but you might not be so lucky.
是啊, 我们全都支持你, 不过你也许 没那么幸运
Andrew.
Andrew
You want to see how long I can hold a grudge?
你想知道我能恨你多久吗?
Go ahead and abandon my father, because I promise you, you'll be sorry.
你尽管抛弃我爸爸好了 但我向你保证, 你会很后悔的
You wouldn't be saying that if you knew what
你不会那么说, 如果你知道
-
knew what?
知道什么?
Well, come on, tell me, because I'd love to know what my father did that was so awful.
拜托, 告诉我, 我想要知道爸爸到底 做了什么糟糕的事情
Fine. I will see him through this, but after that,
好的. 我会照看他直到他康复, 但那之后
your father can rot in hell for all I care.
你爸爸就是死了我也不管
We're not like other families, are we?
我们和其他的家庭不同, 不是吗?
No. We're not.
是的, 我们不同
Gabrielle, it's not my fault that your bank accounts are frozen.
Gabrielle, 你银行账户被冻结不是我的错
I'm not saying it's your fault. I'm just saying fix it.
我并没有说是你的错. 我只是希望你解决它
Well, I wish I could, but the folks at the justice department aren't very sympathetic.
我爱莫能助, 司法部门的那帮家伙 可没有什么同情心
I'm running out of money.
我快没钱了
In a couple of weeks, I'm going to be screwed.
再过几个礼拜我就完了
Why don't you hock some of your jewelry?
你为什么不当掉一些珠宝?
There's a lot of stuff you never wear, and most of it's ugly.
有很多你从来没戴过, 而且大部分都很难看
Don't you have a toilet to scrub?
你不是还有一个卫生间要清洗吗?
I'm just so angry with Carlos.
我真是生Carlos的气
What was he thinking, exporting goods made from slave labor?
竟然进口奴役劳工生产的商品 他在想什么啊?
Why couldn't he have embezzled like other white-collar criminals?
他为什么不能像其他白领罪犯一样 挪用公款呢?
All the justice department wants is to make sure that Carlos doesn't skip the country.
司法部门希望确保Carlos不会潜逃出国
Now, if he's released on bail,
如果他现在能被保释
I can argue that he needs money to live on, and they'll probably unfreeze one of the smaller accounts.
我就能申辩说他需要钱生活, 那么他们 就很可能解冻其中的一个小账户
But they won't release him on bail until they get the passport.
但是除非他们拿到护照, 否则就不可能 保释Carlos
Exactly.
正是
You haven't found that yet, have you?
你还没找到, 是吧?
Gabrielle wanted her old lifestyle back, no question.
(毫无疑问, Gabrielle想要回到原来的生活方式)
But she wanted Carlos to suffer for his betrayal even more.
(但她想让Carlos为自己的背叛多受一些罪)
I'm still searching.
我还在找
Well, in that case, you might want to think about looking for a job.
那样的话你最好考虑找份工作
So I had a really good time.
我度过了一段好时光
Yeah, I bet you did.
是啊, 我想也是
Gotcha.
抓到你了
Hey. Is this a bad time?
嗨. 现在不方便吗?
For you? Of course it is.
对你而言? 当然是了
That's cute. Tax stuff. I need your signature.
聪明. 税务的东西. 我需要你的签名
We've been divorced over a year.
我们已经离婚超过一年了
2003.
2003年
Well, please, just come on in.
请进来吧
Uh, Mike, I don't think you've officially met my ex Karl Mayer.
嗯, Mike, 我想你还没有正式见过 我的前夫Karl Mayer
Oh, hey. Mike Delfino.
哦, 嗨. Mike Delfino
Right. The plumber.
对啊. 水管工
Yeah, I don't have the right washer for this faucet, so I'm just going to go across the street and get it.
是啊. 我找不到这个龙头的垫圈 我到街对面去拿吧
So he seems okay.
他看上去不错
Yeah, he is.
他是不错
So what do you want me to sign?
你想让我签什么?
Oh. I see.
哦. 明白了
By the way, Julie told me about her birthday plans.
顺便说一句, Julie告诉我她的生日计划了
Yeah, we're going to a restaurant downtown.
是的, 我们打算去市中心的饭店
A guy who plays piano and a open Mike.
有人弹钢琴还可以唱歌
Julie got a bunch of her girlfriends together, and so we're just going to make a night of it.
Julie邀请了一堆她的女生朋友 我们打算好好庆祝一下
Julie loves to sing. It sounds nice.
Julie很喜欢唱歌. 那主意听上去不错
Here you go.
给你
All righty.
好的
Give my best to Brandi.
替我向Brandi问好
Actually, uh...
事实上, 嗯...
we're not together anymore.
我们分手了
You're not?
不是吧?
What happened?
发生什么事了?
I caught her in bed with another guy.
我撞见她和另一个男人在床上
Go ahead. Do your happy dance. You deserve it.
没事. 享受你的快乐时光. 你应得的
No, no, really. I'm
不, 真的. 我
- I'm sorry that you had to go through that. I am.
- 我很抱歉你要经历 那些事, 真的
Uh...
嗯...
it's just really hard for me right now.
我现在确实很难过
Thanks.
谢谢
try ripping up old photos. It helps.
可以试一下撕掉那些旧照片. 会好受点
Well, have fun this weekend.
周末愉快
Let me knowhow the party goes.
别忘了告诉我派对过得怎么样
Karl...
do you want to join us?
你想要加入吗?
Susan...
you're the best.
你是最好的
Ooh, well... yeah, I am the best, aren't I?
哦, 嗯... 是啊, 我是最好的, 不是吗?
You know, if we're going to buy a water heater, we should talk about it.
如果要买个热水器, 那我们该谈谈
We could go to the mall tomorrow. They're having a sale.
我们可以明天去商场, 那儿明天降价
Can we talk about this tomorrow?
我们能明天再谈吗?
Well, I'm just trying to plan my day.
我只是想规划一下我的日子
Please, honey, I'm so tired.
拜托, 亲爱的, 我太累了
Okay.
好吧
- Hon?
- 亲爱的?
Hmm?
嗯?
Did you set up the coffee maker?
你装好咖啡壶了吗?
Oh, no.
哦, 没有
You know what? I'll do it in the morning. I promise, I'll get up early and do it.
明早我会弄好的 我保证, 我会早点起来弄好它
- Tom...
mm.
嗯
Tom...come on.
Tom...拜托
Thanks.
谢谢
Yeah.
没关系
C laire?
Claire?
I'm
我
- I'm, uh...
- 我, 恩...
wow, I'm sorry. I didn't know you were up.
喔, 对不起, 我不知道你起来了
Yeah, I- I thought you were sleeping.
是啊, 我以为你们都还睡着
I was just going upstairs.
我正要到楼上去
Do you want me to make the coffee?
你要我泡咖啡吗?
Yeah. Yeah, that'd be great. Yeah.
是的. 是的, 那非常好. 是的
I'm just going to, um, I'm just, you know, go back up to my room.
我正打算, 嗯, 我正打算, 回房间去
Okay.
好的
All right.
Good night.
晚安
Also, you know, if we go to the mall, we can go to the shoe store.
对了, 如果我们去商场, 我们可以 去一下鞋店
You said you wanted new running shoes.
你说你想要新的跑步鞋
What?
什么?
Oh.
哦
The next morning, while the search for Martha Huber continued,
(第二天早上, 当寻找Huber夫人的搜索 还在继续的时候)
Lynette discovered a little family secret
(Lynette发现了一个小小的家庭秘密
-
-)
one she wasn't even looking for.
(一个她想也想不到的秘密)
Good morning.
早上好
Morning.
Want some coffee?
想要些咖啡吗?
Uh, yeah, thanks.
嗯, 好的, 谢谢
I didn't want to come down till Tom left for work.
在Tom去工作前我都不想下来
I'm still a little embarrassed.
我仍然觉得有点尴尬
About what?
为了什么?
Oh, he didn't tell you?
哦, 他没告诉你吗?
Well, actually, it's kind of funny. Um...I was doing some laundry,
实际上, 那有点好笑 恩...我在洗一些衣服
and I noticed that the robe I was wearing had some baby food on it,
我注意到身上的长袍沾到一些婴儿食品
so I threw it in, figuring I could dash upstairs while everyone was asleep,
所以我把它扔进了洗衣机, 我想我可以 趁大家睡觉的时候冲回楼上去
and then I ran into Tom
然后我遇到了Tom
while I was totally naked.
我当时全身赤裸
And so, Claire, when did this incident occur?
那么, Claire, 这事什么时候发生的?
I don't know. It was pretty late.
我不知道. 已经很晚了
I think he might have come down to make coffee or something.
我想他可能是下来煮咖啡什么的
You don't say.
不会吧
Wow.
喔
Wow. Well, this is certainly impressive. I can definitely get you work as a model,
喔. 这真是令人印象深刻 我绝对可以给你找一份模特工作
but you do realize it's different from the runway work you did in New York and Milan.
但你应该清楚这儿和你以前在纽约 米兰做的不同
Of course. I made $10,000 a day.
当然. 我以前赚1万美金一天
I don't expect to
我不期望
-to make that here.
-在这儿能赚那么多
Well, that's good, because you won't.
那很好, 因为你赚不到
Yeah. So what do you got?
那你有什么工作?
Well, there is something.
有一些
Uh, they need a model to demonstrate the new buick lacrosse at the fairview mall.
fairview商场需要一个展示新型buick lacrosse的车模
It's just going to be you and the car on a revolving platform. 300 bucks for the day.
就你和车在旋转平台上, 300美金一天
Uh, what else do you have?
嗯, 还有其它的吗?
Sure.
当然
Um... ooh. Can you swing a sword?
嗯... 你会舞剑吗?
Sci-fi convention needs someone to dress up as a warrior princess.
科幻小说大会需要有人装扮成一个 战士公主
A warrior princess?
一个战士公主?
Mr. Gibb, I am a professional model.
Gibb先生, 我是个职业模特
Look at this bone structure.
看看这骨架
This face is a cash cow.
这张脸蛋就是财源啊
And if you don't have the vision to take advantage of that, then maybe I'm at the wrong agency.
如果你没有眼光来好好利用 我想我是走错地方了
Hey, look, honey,
嗨, 你看, 宝贝儿
I'm the only modeling agent in a 100-mile radius.
我是方圆一百里内唯一的模特经纪人
I book women for boat shows and garden tool expos.
我为船展和园林工具展签模特
If you don't like it, move back to the city.
如果你不喜欢, 你就回城里去吧
This, um, buick thing...
这个, 嗯, buick的活动...
does it include lunch?
包不包中饭?
Just so you know,
只是想让你知道
I really am grateful for everything you're doing for me.
我很感激你为我做的一切
Oh, I don't need your gratitude.
哦, 我不需要你的感激
You're only here because your children are master extortionists.
你在这里的唯一原因是你的孩子们 都是一流的勒索者
So you didn't tell them about
你没告诉他们
-
your adultery? No, I decided to keep that little gem all to myself.
你的通奸行为? 不, 我决定把这块“宝石” 留给自己
Listen, I know this is a real imposition
听着, 我知道这是真正的强迫接受
-
yes, it is.
是的, 这是
The doctor said you could be here for weeks.
医生说你可能要在这儿呆好几个礼拜
Would it make you feel any better if I told you I'm sorry for what I did?
如果我告诉你我对所做的事情很抱歉 会不会让你觉得好过些?
Yes, it would...
是的, 那会...
if I still felt anything for you.
如果我对你还有任何感觉的话
But as it stands, the place you used to occupy in my heart is very much empty now.
但事实是, 你过去在我心里的位置 现在已经空了
You must still feel something for me.
你肯定对我还有感觉
And why do you think that?
你为什么那么想?
Oh, come on. Bree, look at this.
哦, 拜托. Bree, 看看这一切
You're using the good china,freshly pressed napkins, flowers from the garden.
你用了好的瓷器, 刚刚压过的餐巾 花园里的鲜花
This tray was prepared with loving care.
你用一份爱心准备了这个盘子
Do me a favor, Rex
帮我个忙, Rex
-
please don't mistake my anal retentiveness for actual affection.
不要把肛门的保持力和真正的情感搞错了
Hold on a sec.
等一下
Okay. Now I'm good.
好. 现在我感觉好多了
What?
什么?
You're just
你真是
-god, I love you.
-天啊, 我爱你
Oh.
哦
Well...that's great.
嗯...那很好
Wait, look, that just kind of popped out.
等一下, 那其实是我不小心说出来了
No, no, it's fine. It just kind of caught me off-guard.
不, 不, 那很好. 那有一点趁人不备
I mean, I want to say it back.
我是说, 我也想对你那么说
Yeah, but you're not ready. It's okay.
是啊, 但你还没准备好. 那没关系
You're not mad, are you?
你没有发疯, 是吧?
No, god. We haven't even been dating that long, and you've got other issues. I get it.
没有, 上帝. 我们那么长时间没约会了 你一直在忙别的事情. 我明白
Good.
很好
Issues? What kind of issues do you think I have?
事情? 你觉得我有什么事情?
You know, I retract my earlier statement. I no longer love you.
我说, 我收回原来的话, 我不再爱你
In fact, I just think of you as a really good buddy.
事实上, 我只是把你看做是一个很好的伙伴
No. No, no, no, no. You obviously think you have some insight into my soul,
不. 不, 不, 不, 不. 很明显你觉得 你看穿了我
so please go ahead. Dazzle me.
那么来吧, 说说看
Your divorce left you hurt and vulnerable.
离婚伤害了你, 使你易受伤害
Big insight. The postman knows that.
好厉害. 这个连邮差都知道
And there's a chance you might still have feelings for your ex.
你有可能对你的前夫仍有感觉
What?
什么?
I loathe Karl,
我厌恶Karl
and the postman will back me up on that, too.
邮差也会同意那一点
I'm sure part of you does hate him, but, well, maybe part of you is still hung up on him.
我相信部分的你确实恨他, 但, 嗯 还有部分的你依然挂念他
Where are you getting this?
你从哪儿看出来的?
Well, he broke up with the woman he left you for,
你前夫和那个他为其抛弃家庭的女人分手
and what was the first thing you did? You hugged him
而你做的第一件事是什么? 你拥抱了他
and invited him to a party.
而且邀请他来派对
Okay.
好吧
The analysis part of this evening is now over.
今晚的分析部分结束了
Hey... you asked.
嗨... 是你要问的
Well, you know what?
你知道吗?
You're going to come to julie's party tomorrow night,
明天晚上你要来参加Julie的派对
and you're going to see Karl and I together,
你会看到我和Karl
and you're going to understand once and for all that I have no feelings for him whatsoever.
然后你就会明白我对他什么感觉都没有
Well, actually, I have tickets to a basketball game
事实上, 我买了篮球赛的票
-
well, actually, you're coming to the party tomorrow, and that's the end of it.
事实上, 你明天来参加派对, 说定了
This is what I get for saying "I love you."
这就是我说了“我爱你”所换来的
What?
什么?
Nothing.
没什么
There you go.
给你
Hello, George.
你好, George
Mrs. Van De Kamp. You're looking lovely today.
Van De Kamp夫人. 你今天看上去很可爱
You always say the nicest things.
你总是说最动听的话
Well, it's, uh, it's true.
嗯, 那, 嗯, 的确是
Listen, I have a prescription here for Rex. I don't know if you heard, but he had a heart attack.
你看, 我有给Rex的处方 我不知道你是否听说了, Rex心脏病发了
I had no idea. Is he okay?
我不知道. 他没事吧?
Oh, yes, he'll
是的, 他
-he'll live, but, uh, the doctor says he's at risk for something called pericarditis.
-他会活下来, 但是, 嗯 医生说他有可能会有包心炎
Do you know anything about that?
你对那个有了解吗?
It's an inflammation of the membrane that surrounds the heart.
那是心脏周围隔膜的一种炎症
It'll take a few months to make sure it doesn't develop, but he'll need constant care.
需要几个月来确定病情不再发展 但他需要持续护理
So I hear.
和我听说的一样
As the words "constant care" echoed in her head,
(随着“持续护理”这个词在她的脑子里回响)
Bree caught a sickening glimpse into her future...
(Bree瞥到了她令人作呕的未来...)
okay, here we go.
好了, 给你
Which prompted her to seek an old-fashioned remedy.
(而那促使她寻找一种古老的补救方法)
George, would you go out to dinner with me?
George, 你想和我共进晚餐吗?
Um, y-you mean like a date?
嗯, 你的意思是约会?
Yes. I think it would be fun.
是的. 我想那会很有意思
What about your husband?
你丈夫怎么办?
Oh, him.
哦, 他
Well, we're separated.
我们分居了
In spite of Mrs. Huber's disappearance, life on Wisteria Lane started to return to normal
(尽管Huber夫人依然失踪 但Wisteria Lane开始恢复平常的生活)
until an intriguing discovery was made on a dirt road next to the interstate.
(直到州际公路边的泥路上的一个 有趣的发现)
This is officer burton.
我是Burton警官
I have an abandoned vehicle registered to a missing person. One Martha Huber. Please advise.
我发现一部遗弃车辆, 登记人为一个失踪者 名为Martha Huber, 请告知有关情况
As news spread of this mysterious development, everyone in the neighborhood decided to band together
(随着这个神秘发现消息的传播 邻居们决定团结起来)
to show their support and to look for clues...
(表现他们的支持, 并寻找线索...)
or worse.
(或更坏的事物)
I'm keeping my eyes on the horizon.
我注意着水平线上的事物
Please tell me if I am about to step on a body part.
如果我踩到身体的一部分, 请告诉我
It's a search and rescue, not recover. We don't know if she's dead.
现在是寻找和救援, 不是发现 我们还不知道她是否死了
Yeah, people fake their own abductions all the time.
是啊, 人们经常伪装被绑架
Could we talk about something else, something less depressing?
我们能不能谈些不太令人沮丧的事情?
Well, here's something
对了, 我有事情
- Mike told me he loved me.
- Mike对我说他爱我
Oh, my god!
哦, 天啊!
Over here! They found the body!
在这儿! 他们找到了尸体!
No, I'm sorry! False alarm! We didn't find a body.
不, 对不起! 弄错了! 我们没找到尸体
Uh, Susan just had some really good news.
嗯, Susan有一些很好的消息
- Sorry.
- 对不起
It was nothing. False alarm.
没关系. 弄错了而已
Well, doesn't that figure. Susan always finds a way to make it about her.
那真是不出所料. Susan总是有办法炫耀自己
Ladies and gentlemen, I present to you the fabulous buick lacrosse.
女士们先生们, 我向你们展示迷人的 buick lacrosse
It
它
- it has expertly crafted interior,
- 它有精心打造的内部空间
peaceful, quiet tuning, and ultra sonic rear parking assist.
宁静, 无声发动机调整, 还有 超声波后停车支持
Observe the remote activation feature.
请注意看遥控启动装置
Uh, and it also has a lot of other exciting, good, cool car things.
嗯, 它还有另外很多精彩的, 好的 酷的汽车玩意儿
Tom, Lynette. What are you doing here?
Tom, Lynette. 你们在这里干嘛呢?
We're buying a new water heater. Um, how about you?
我们在买一个新热水器. 嗯, 你呢?
Just doing a little shopping, trying to get my mind off things.
买些东西, 让我的脑子轻松一下
Hey, Gabby, you need help? It looks like you're stuck here.
嗨, Gabby, 你需要帮助吗? 看上去你困在这儿了
Oh, I guess I am.
我想是的
- No worries. I got it.
- 别担心. 我来
Guess I got too close to the turntable.
我猜我和旋转台离得太近了
I'm a sucker for these buicks.
我一点都不懂这些buick车
Come on, you bastard.
拜托, 你这个混蛋
You know, with their, uh, perfectly crafted interior and peaceful, quiet tuning.
你知道, 它们, 嗯, 完美打造的内部 和安静无声的发动机调整
Uh-huh.
嗯
Little formal for the mall.
对于逛商场而言过于正式了
Oh, uh, you know, I-I wanted to match the shoes to the dress.
哦, 嗯, 我想使鞋和衣服配得上
This is, uh, sarah,
这位是, 嗯, sarah
my shopping buddy. We like to hitthe boutiques together.
和我一起购物的伙伴 我们喜欢一起去逛专卖店
Okay, well, you gals, um, shop your little hearts out. See you later.
那么, 女孩子们, 嗯, 尽情购物吧 再见
Bye.
再见
Wow. Look at you. You going out?
喔. 看看你. 你要出去?
Not that it's any of your business, but, um, I have a date.
不关你的事, 不过, 嗯, 我有个约会
A date? What kind of date?
约会? 哪种约会?
Rex, I don't want to say anything that might upset you.
Rex, 我不想说任何会让你不开心的事情
The doctor says any undue stress could cause another heart attack.
医生说压力过大心脏病会再次发作的
It's a romantic date with a single, attractive man, and I intend to french the hell out of him.
那是和一个单身有魅力的男人的浪漫约会 我真想把他给生吃了
Oh, right on time.
哦, 时间正好
- Hi.
- 嗨.
Hi.
嗨.
In my spare time, I garden. I thought you might like these.
在我有空的时候, 我做一些园艺. 我想你也许会喜欢这些
Oh, my. They're exquisite.
哦, 天啊. 它们真精致
Compost and eggshells?
混合肥料和蛋壳?
Yes.
是的
Oh. Come on in.
哦. 请进
Thanks.
谢谢
George, you remember Rex.
George, 你记得Rex
Uh, I thought you said you were separated.
嗯, 我以为你说你们分居了
Oh, we are, emotionally. Physically, he just lives here because his mistress refuses to care for him.
哦, 是的, 情感上. 物质上, 他住在这儿 是因为他的情人不愿意照顾他
Would you like a drink?
你想喝些什么?
Uh, no, I-I'm fine, thanks.
嗯, 不了, 我很好, 谢谢
Rex, say hello to George.
Rex, 跟George打个招呼
Hello, George.
你好, George
Hello, Dr. Van De Kamp.
你好, Van De Kamp医生
I'm going to go put these in water.
我把这些放到水里去
George, why don't you have a seat, and I'll be right back?
George, 你随便坐, 我马上就回来
So, uh, how's your heart, Dr. Van De Kamp?
嗯, 你的心脏怎么样, Van De Kamp医生?
- Better. How's the pharmacy?
- 好些了. 药店怎么样?
Busy. It's busy.
忙. 很忙
Is something funny?
有什么可笑的事情吗?
It's
不
- it's nothing.
- 没什么
See, I, uh...I recently engaged in some extracurricular activity,
你看, 我, 嗯...我最近参加了一些 “课外活动”
and now bree's doing anything she can to make me suffer
现在Bree就想尽办法让我难过
All you can do is laugh.
你所能做的就是笑
Yeah. I-I guess.
是的. 我想是的
Oh, these flowers are stunning. They're the best ones I've ever gotten.
哦, 这些话太漂亮了 是我收到过的最好的花
Shall we?
我们走吧?
Well, it was nice talking to you, Dr. Van De Kamp.
嗯, 很高兴与你交谈, Van De Kamp医生
Please. You're dating my wife. Call me Rex.
拜托. 你在和我的妻子约会. 叫我Rex就行了
That salesgirl that sold us the water heater
那个卖热水器给我们的销售小姐
- she had a cute figure.
- 她长得很不错啊
Yeah, I guess. I didn't notice.
我想是吧. 我没注意
Oh, how can you say? She was so your type-- big breasts, really curvy.
哦, 怎么可能? 她是你喜欢的那一种-- 胸部丰满, 曲线优美
What are you doing?
你干嘛?
Nothing. I'm just saying you prefer women who are really curvy, women like that salesgirl or Claire.
没什么. 我说你喜欢曲线好的女人 比如那个销售小姐或者Claire
There's only one type that I prefer.
我只喜欢一种类型
You.
你
Aw, you kissed me as though that would end this conversation, and it so won't.
哦, 你吻了我就好像这个对话结束了 那还没完呢
Why am I in trouble? I haven't done anything wrong.
为什么我有麻烦了? 我又没做错什么
The only reason you made love to me the other night was because you had just seen claire naked.
你那晚和我做爱的唯一原因是因为 你刚刚看到了Claire的裸体
aw, crap.
噢, 废话
Claire is a great nanny. It would be stupid to lose her over something like this.
Claire是个好保姆. 如果因为这个 失去她的话那真是太蠢了
You and I have had crushes before. We always tell each other.
你和我都喜欢过别人, 我们告诉对方
We laugh about it. It's no big deal.
我们一起说说笑笑就过去了 没什么大不了的
What worries me about this is you're denying you're obviously attracted. Why?
这次让我感到担心的是你明显被吸引 而你否认. 为什么?
I'm not denying anything.
我没有否认任何事
Oh, so you are attracted to her.
哦, 那你被她吸引了
I didn't say that.
我没说
What are you doing?
你干嘛?
We are not going anywhere until you confess you have the hots for our nanny.
在你承认你被我们的保姆吸引之前 我们哪儿也不去
Tom, it's okay. She's attractive.
Tom, 没关系. 她很诱人
Men by nature are drawn to fertile young women with whom they can plant their seed.
男人天生就想在年轻女人身上播种
It's the basic flaw of your gender. I get it. Just do me the honor of
那是你们性别的根本缺陷 我明白. 只要让我
-
we'd all like to get out of here. Is there a problem?
我们都想离开这儿. 有什么问题吗?
My husband won't admit that he has lust in his heart.
我丈夫不承认他心里有淫欲
Can you give us a minute?
你能给我们一点时间吗?
Lynette, Claire is attractive, yes.
Lynette, Claire是很吸引人, 是的
But I am not attracted to her.
但我没被她吸引
Look, if I thought for even a second that there was any danger in having Claire around,
我说, 如果我有一丝念头想到Claire 在周围会有事情发生
I'd be the first to get rid of her.
我第一个就会辞退她
It's you. You're the one.
是你. 你是我喜欢的
You always have been, and you always will be.
一直是你, 永远是你
All right. Hold your water.
好吧. 合情合理
Then as a coda, we drink ice cream soda here down at the old five and dime, yeah
“Then as a coda, we drink ice cream soda here down at the old five and dime, yeah”
yay. Oh, you guys were fantastic.
耶. 哦, 你们太棒了
Thank you.
谢谢
Um, they've got a dance floor upstairs, and we're going to go check it out.
嗯, 楼上可以跳舞, 我们要去看看
Okay. Have fun.
好的, 玩得开心点
Edie. Over here.
Edie. 来这儿
What the hell is she doing here?
她在这儿干嘛?
What, I don't get to bring a date? I heard you were bringing him.
怎么, 我不能带个伴来吗? 我听说你们邀请他了
Of all people, you pick that tired piece of
在所有人中, 你挑了那个
-
- Edie.
Hi, Susan.
嗨, Susan
Oh, thank you so much for the invite.
哦, 多谢你邀请我
God knows I needed something to get my mind off poor Martha.
我真是需要一些事情来帮我 暂时忘记Martha
A kiss for the birthday boy.
给生日男孩一个吻
Um, Edie, it's not his birthday.
嗯, Edie, 不是他过生日
Oh. Oh.
哦. 哦
Thank you, George. That was a lovely evening.
谢谢, George. 真是个美好的夜晚
The pleasure was mine.
那是我的荣幸
There's nothing better than great conversation with a beautiful woman over a delicious meal.
没有哪个对话能比在可口的饭菜前 和一个美丽的女人更好了
Well, I guess I should go inside.
那么, 我想我该进去了
I'm glad we did this.
我很高兴我们这么做了
Me too.
我也是
Andrew. Where did you come from?
Andrew. 你从哪儿来的?
I was just on my wayback from brian's house. What's going on here?
我刚从Brian家回来, 你们在干什么?
Oh, uh, you remember Mr. Williams, our pharmacist.
哦, 你记得Williams先生吗 我们的药物师
- Hey there.
- 你好
How's it going?
你好吗?
What are you doing in his car?
你在他车里干什么?
We're just, um, talking. Mr. Williams took me out to dinner.
我们在, 嗯, 交谈 Williams先生邀请我去晚餐了
You mean like on a date?
你是说约会?
Well, um...
嗯...
Yes.
是的
You are aware that she's married, right?
你知道她已经结婚了, 对吗?
Andrew, your father and I are separated, and you know it.
Andrew, 你爸爸和我分居了, 你知道的
I don't care. Couldn't you at least wait until he was out of the house?
我不管. 你就不能等到他搬出去吗?
The only reason he's still in the house is because you insisted I care for him.
他在家里的唯一原因是你要我照看他
So
那么
- so what, what are you guys going to do now?
- 你们打算怎么做?
Are you
你们
- are you two going to have sex?
- 你们准备做爱?
- No, we are not going to have sex.
- 不, 我们不会做爱
Why not?
为什么不?
Because I don't commit adultery like your father.
因为我不像你爸爸那样通奸
That's right. Your father had an affair, I found out about it, and I'm just trying to move on with my life.
是的, 你爸爸有外遇, 我发现了 而我试图继续我的生活
You should watch out for her. She's a liar.
你应该当心点她, 她是个骗子
Andrew...
In spite of her mounting debt,
(尽管她的债务与日俱增)
Gabrielle was determined to prove she could get along just fine without Carlos's money.
(Gabrielle决心证明没有Carlos的钱 她也能过得很好)
It wasn't until the electricity went out
(但直到停电了)
that she finally began to see the light.
(她才幡然醒悟)
Mr. Hartley, it's Gabrielle Solis.
Hartley先生, 我是Gabrielle Solis
I need you to start working on releasing Carlos on bail.
我需要你立刻着手Carlos的保释
I just remembered where I put his passport.
我刚想起来我把护照放哪里了
But I, I took the sweet life
never knew I'd be bitter from the sweet
I spent my life exploring the subtle whoring
that costs too much to be free
hey, lady
I've been to paradise
but I've never been
to me
Oh, thank you.
哦, 谢谢
Damn, woman. You were good.
哦, 你太棒了
Yes. All right, you're next, susie Q. What you going to sing?
好, 你是下一个, susie Q. 你唱什么?
Yes
好
You sing?
你唱歌?
Only when I'm alone.
只有我一个人的时候
Come on. We're among friends.
拜托. 我们都不是外人
I don't think so.
我不这么认为
Well, I, for one, would love to hear your voice.
我, 算一个, 想听你唱歌
Give it up, plumber. She's not budging.
算了吧, 管道工. 她不会唱的
You want to hear me sing?
你想听我唱歌?
Yeah.
是的
Okay.
好的
What's it going to be? I'll tell the piano player.
唱什么? 我去告诉钢琴师
"New york, new york."
“New york, new york”
Oh, I am so excited to hear you.
能听你唱歌我真是兴奋啊
Oh, but doesn't it just figure?
哦, 不过那不是正好吗?
What do you mean?
你什么意思?
You have to get up in front of a room full of people dressed like that.
你穿着这样的衣服在一个全是人的房间 站在大家面前演唱
I hope they don't turn on you.
我希望他们不会被你挑逗起来
I think I'll take my chances, sort of like you did on those high notes.
我想我会试试看的, 像你刚才的那些 高音一样
I'm going to get us two more.
我再去给我们那两杯来
That's a great idea.
很好
So that Mike
那么Mike
- he seems pretty even-keeled.
- 他看起来很稳健
Yeah. He's a great guy.
是啊, 他是个好男人
But you know, I mean, he's a little buster brown.
但你知道, 我的意思是, 褐色的家伙
Don't you ever worry you're going to get bored?
你没担心过有一天会厌倦吗?
Thanks for your concern, Karl. I'm fine.
谢谢你的关心, Karl. 我很好
Go figure.
那就好
Even though our marriage was crazy at times, it never got dull.
尽管我们的婚姻有时疯狂, 但从不单调
Yeah, that part when you slept with your secretary was really exciting.
是啊, 你和你秘书睡觉的部分真是刺激啊
I know. How many times do I have to hear it? It was a mistake.
我知道, 我还要听几次啊? 那是个错误
But don't I ever get credit for the 13 loyal years beforehand?
但我不该为13年的忠诚婚姻得到些表扬吗?
You must not be counting the Hendersons' christmas party.
你们不是在数Henderson的圣诞晚会吧
Edie, not now.
Edie, 不是现在
Oh, what's the big deal, Karl? Your marriage is history anyway.
哦, 怎么了, Karl? 你的婚姻已经是历史了
Edie.
Edie
It was nothing, really. Basically, we both got plastered on eggnog,
那没什么, 真的 我们只是都受到了巨大打击
and we found ourselves standing under the, uh, mistletoe,
我们发现自己站在槲寄生下
and we were like, "okay, well, what do we do now?"
我们就像, “好吧, 我们接下来做什么”
So I smiled, and he smiled, and then Karl reached over and started feeling me up.
然后我笑了, 他也笑了, 然后Karl 过来开始爱抚我
- Susie, that's not how it happened.
- Susie, 不是那样的
All right, Susan, come on, you're up.
好吧, Susan, 来吧, 轮到你了
What?
什么?
This is
这
-it's so silly.
-太无聊了
Susie
-
Ladies and gentlemen, please welcome Susan Mayer.
女士们先生们, 请欢迎Susan Mayer
Start spreadin' the news
I'm leavin' today
I wanna be a part of it
new york, new york
these vagabond shoes
you're an ass, you know that? No, keep playing.
你是个混蛋, 你知道吗? 不, 请继续演奏
Are longing to stray
there's a word, you know, right?
And get around the heart of it
new york, new york
I wanna
just tell you that the affair was one thing.
告诉你那个外遇是一回事
I mean, I forgave you, because on some small level,
我是说, 我原谅你, 因为只是那种程度
I thought that you were in love with her,
我以为你爱她
and now I find out that you were just groping people at parties.
现在我发觉你只是在派对上找女人
Top of the heap
Karl, don't you turn away from me. Look at me!
Karl, 你别转过头去. 看着我!
You know, what else were you doing during our marriage?
你知道我们还结婚的时候你还做过什么?
How many other women were you sticking it to?
你和多少女人混过?
As god is my witness, it will snow on the hills of hell before I ever feel sorry for you again!
上帝作证, 除非地狱之山下雪了 否则我再也不会为你难过了!
New york
As the police interviewed the residents of Wisteria Lane about the mysterious disappearance of Martha Huber,
(当警察开始询问Wisteria Lane的居民们 有关Martha Huber神秘失踪的事情时)
my husband Paul reasoned it would only be a matter of time before their digging would begin to yield answers.
(我的丈夫Paul意识到警察的调查 很快就会有结果)
Since he knew the police had no suspects,
(既然他知道警察还没发现嫌疑犯)
he decided to point them towards the most logical candidate.
(他决定把他们引向最合乎逻辑的人选)
You see, if there's one thing Paul understood about the suburbs, it was this
(你看, 如果说Paul对于郊区有一点了解 那就是
-
-)
no one's ever more suspicious
(没有人比)
than a new neighbor who's just moved in.
(刚搬进来的人更可疑了)
Parker's getting sniffly.
Parker开始抽鼻子了
Yeah, I noticed that, too. I hope he's not coming down with a cold.
是啊, 我也注意到了, 希望他不要感冒
He doesn't have a cough yet, but he sort of has this post-nasal drip thing happening.
他还没咳嗽, 但他开始流鼻涕了
I'll make an appointment for him.
我去和医生预约一下
I always say it is better to be safe than sorry.
我一直认为安全比后悔更重要
Little kids get sick, and it's
小孩子生病, 那是
- sorry
- 对不起
-out of control...
- 无法控制的...
man, kids with these colds, it's just
嗨, 感冒了的孩子
- just this vicious cycle.
- 那是恶性循环
Um, um, Claire?
嗯, 嗯, Claire?
We have to make some changes.
我们要做一些变化
What are you doing?
你在干什么?
I'm packing up your father's things for when he eventually moves out.
我在整理你爸爸最终搬出去时带的东西
Well, here. Let me help you.
我来帮你吧
Look, I-I talked to dad,
我和爸爸谈过了
and it turns out you were telling the truth.
原来你说的是真的
Oh, andrew, I'm so sorry that I said anything.
哦, andrew, 我真抱歉告诉你那些事
No, you know, I'm glad you did. Now I know.
不, 我很高兴你那么做. 现在我知道了
There comes this point in every boy's life.
每个男孩都会经历这个时刻
What, finding out his dad's screwing around?
什么时刻, 发现他的爸爸到处乱搞?
No.
不
That his father's only human.
发现他的爸爸也只是个普通人
Listen, why are you taking care of him?
那你为什么照看他?
Is it because of what Danielle and I said? Because you can forget that.
是因为Danielle和我说的话吗? 你可以忘了那些话
I'll help you take his stuff out on the street if you want.
我可以帮你把他的东西搬到街上去
That's sweet, but I'm taking care of him because it's the right thing to do.
你真好, 不过我照看他是因为 我应该那么做
Why are you being such a push over?
你为什么表现得如此软弱?
I mean, he cheated on you.
我的意思是, 他欺骗了你
He's a jerk.
他是个混蛋
Andrew...
you will not speak that way about your father in front of me.
你不许在我面前这样说你爸爸
Why the hell not? I mean, for once, I'm actually on your side.
为什么不行? 这次我真的是站在你这边
Yes, I'm angry with him.
是的, 我很气他
I am going to divorce him. I may even marry somebody else.
我会和他离婚. 我也许和别人结婚
But make no mistake about it, your father is and always will be the love of my life.
但是不要弄错, 你爸爸现在是, 以后 永远都是我的爱
He gave me the best18-year marriage that...
他给了我最好的18年婚姻...
I could have ever hoped for.
我所能期望的最好的
And for that, you will respect him.
就为了那个, 你该尊敬他
Okay
好吧
What is it? I'm really, really busy.
什么事? 我真的很忙
I came by to apologize.
我是来道歉的
Oh. Well, in that case, come on in. I'm not doing anything.
哦. 这样的话, 进来吧. 我一点都不忙
I can't believe Edie brought the whole thing up.
我不敢相信Edie会把事情都说出来
Susan... I-I am so sorry.
Susan... 对不起
I-I thought I was done hurting you.
我觉得我伤害了你
Yeah, me too.
我也是
And just so you know,
只是想让你知道
I'm sorry for flipping out.
我很抱歉在派对上失态了
I shouldn't let you get to me like that.
我不应该让你那样影响我
What?
什么?
I do still get to you, don't I?
我依然对你有影响, 不是吗?
That's the difference between the plumber and me.
那是我和水管工的区别
No, don't get me wrong, he's a good guy. I mean, I like him.
不, 别误解, 他是个好人, 我喜欢他
But I'm betting that you two don't have what we had together.
但我敢打赌你们没有我们之间有的东西
There was always a spark between us.
我们之间总是有火花
A spark?
火花?
Look, what I'm trying to say is he must seem really safe after me.
我想说的是在经历我的事情后 你肯定觉得他很有安全感
A moray eel would seem safe after you.
一条海鳗都比你有安全感
That's what I'm talking about
那正是我想说的
- that great back-and-forth, the joking around...
- 那种针锋相对 开着玩笑...
we still argue and push each other's buttons.
我们依然争吵
News flash
告诉你
-I hated all of that.
-我讨厌那些事情
Come on, you have to admit when it was good,
拜托, 你必须承认以前的好时光
it was the best.
是最美好的
What are you saying?
你在说什么啊?
Let's give this another shot.
让我们再试一次吧
You want me back?
你想我回来吗?
Yeah.
是啊
Yeah. I realize now
是的, 我现在意识到了
that you were the woman that was meant for me.
你才是我命中注定的女人
Wow.
喔
W-w-- just so we're clear,
喔-- 那明说吧
so
你
- so you want to move back in here and
- 你想要搬回来
- and be faithful to me and love me with all your heart and soul?
- 并且全心全意地忠诚于我和爱我吗?
Absolutely.
当然了
Oh, my god. This is so wonderful.
哦, 天啊. 这太妙了
Yeah. I know, I know.
是啊. 我知道, 我知道
I want to kiss you.
我想吻你
Oh, god. No, Karl. Um, no,
哦, 天啊. 不, Karl. 嗯, 不,
what I meant by wonderful was that I wondered inside if I still had feelings for you, if deep down, I still loved you.
我说太妙了是因为我不知道我是否对你 还有感觉, 不知道内心深处是否仍然爱你
And?
然后?
And
然后
-
There's nothing there.
没什么感觉了
Come on. You've got to feel something.
拜托. 你肯定还有感觉
Well, actually, I do, yeah. Excuse me.
是啊, 实际上, 我是还有. 不好意思
Oh, my god.
哦, 上帝啊
Susan.
Susan
Mike, guess what.
Mike, 你猜怎样
I love you.
我爱你
Are you sure?
你确定?
Yes.
是的
Did I come at a bad time?
我来得不是时候?
Um, they're just asking some questions about Mrs. Huber.
嗯, 他们在问一些有关Huber夫人的问题
I love him. You can write that in your little book.
我爱他. 你可以把它写在你的小本子里
We are all searching for someone,
(我们都在寻找一个人)
that special person who will provide us what's missing in our lives.
(他能带来我们生活中所缺少的东西)
Someone who can offer companionship...
(有些人能提供陪伴...)
George? Hi, it's me
George? 嗨, 是我
- Bree.
- Bree
I was wondering, are you free next saturday?
我在想, 你下周六有空吗?
You are? Oh, that's wonderful.
你有空? 那太好了
Or assistance...
(或是帮助...)
hi. I understand your agency handles nannies.
嗨. 我知道你们公司提供保姆
I need someone experienced and preferably unattractive.
我需要有经验而且最好是没有吸引力的人
Or security.
(或是安全)
Hi, honey. Did the lawyer tell you the good news?
嗨, 亲爱的. 律师告诉你什么好消息了吗?
You're going to make bail. I found your passport.
你可以被保释了. 我找到了你的护照
And sometimes, if we search very hard, we can find someone who provides us...
(有时候如果努力寻找, 我们能找到...)
well, I just called to say hi, and I love you.
嗯, 我只是打个招呼, 我爱你
With all three.
(能同时提供以上三者的人)
All right, all right. Enough already.
好了, 好了. 够了
Yes, we're all searching for someone,
(是的, 我们都在寻找一个人)
and if we can't find them,
(如果我们找不到他们)
we can only pray
(那我们只能祈祷)
they find us.
(他们会找到我们)